{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Nguyen",
    "predicate": "ontology/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Filmmaking",
    "human_readable": "Paul Nguyen's occupation is filmmaking.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9397017955780029,
            "question": "Does Paul Nguyen make movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8331316113471985,
            "question": "What is Paul Nguyen's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7612435221672058,
            "question": "Has Paul Nguyen won any awards for his filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7202993035316467,
            "question": "What industry is Paul Nguyen involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6697726845741272,
            "question": "What kind of work does Paul Nguyen create?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5735260844230652,
            "question": "What is Paul Nguyen known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5235358476638794,
            "question": "Is Paul Nguyen an artist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45256850123405457,
            "question": "What are some examples of Paul Nguyen's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4293186366558075,
            "question": "Where does Paul Nguyen work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2800678610801697,
            "question": "What does Paul Nguyen do for a living?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Nguyen's occupation is filmmaking.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1748_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does Paul Nguyen work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1748_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of Paul Nguyen's work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1748_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Paul Nguyen an artist?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1748_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_154.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1748_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\n* The documents mention that Paul Nguyen is a filmmaker, journalist and social activist (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1748/re-ranker-msmarco/62.txt).\n* Additionally, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1748/re-ranker-msmarco/111.txt and 123.txt also mention that Paul Nguyen is a professional photographer, but this does not contradict the information in the first document."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Paul Nguyen is a filmmaker, journalist, and social activist. Therefore, the statement \"Paul Nguyen's occupation is filmmaking\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}